wasteland.com 2018-11-05

# Fetish Porn | Bondage | BDSM | Hardcore Sex Movies | Wasteland.com - Darker Side of Desire

Wasteland Privacy Policy

Last Updated: April 30, 2018

This site is wholly-owned by WASTELAND, Inc.

Preamble and General Principles

The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy describes how our company and all of its properties operated under these names, hereinafter known as "WASTELAND," collects information from all end-users of WASTELAND's Internet services (the "Services") - those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay fees to gain access to the Service ("Members") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members ("Users") have concerning the collection and use of such information. WASTELAND requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Revisions to this Policy

WASTELAND reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user's browser. The user should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after the user has clicked the "refresh" button on his/her browser, the user may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" date indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting.

Personal Information WASTELAND Collects and How It Is Used

WASTELAND collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected when we believe that such disclosure is required by law.

Registration: Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, billing information (such as a credit card number), and email adress. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is collected by our credit card processors, and is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.

Online Advertisements

WASTELAND displays online advertisements. We are not affiliated with these third-party websites and are not responsible for their use of information.

Responses to Email Inquiries

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to WASTELAND's websites, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. WASTELAND does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

Voluntary Customer Surveys

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

Other Internet Data

WASTELAND also collects IP addresses, referral URLs, browser preferences, the user's registration forms, surveys, and communications transmitted through site applications. This information is used internally to track how users come to be referred to our Sites for the purpose of compensating our affiliates, advertisers, and other marketing entities. This information may be disclosed to third-parties. If we choose to disclose information to third-parties, this information shall consist of non-specific information regarding site traffic and statistics. WASTELAND never discloses any customer-specific information to third parties unless it is reasonable to believe that doing so is required by law, a binding contract, a Court Order, or other state, local, or administrative regulation.

As a service to our users we sometimes provide links to various third party web sites in our email communications. We are neither responsible for the content on nor for the information collection practices of such web sites, nor do we control the privacy policies of such web sites. Their policies may be substantially different in this regard from WASTELAND. We also use Google Analytics to collect basic usage data on our tour which does not capture any identifiable surfer information, but rather trafic volume, time spent on site, bounce rate and traffic vocume rankings by country of origin.

At times, WASTELAND may enter into co-branding arrangements with other companies, and if so, an opt-in or opt-out question may be present to allow email contact from these companies as well. Their opt-in/out features are specific to each organization, but you should not receive email from these organizations unless you have indicated that it is acceptable. Before consenting to receive email from third parties, you should read their privacy policy and terms of use, if applicable, to make sure you are comfortable dealing with that company. As you can understand, WASTELAND can not make commitments on behalf of other companies. All email from WASTELAND partners who gain your permission to send you commercial email, will include an opportunity to opt out of future communications.

Our Commitment to Children's Protection

Our sites are designed for adults, and not for use by anyone under the age of 18. 

We have no Web pages designed for younger users. We make every effort to ensure that our Web sites contain adequate warnings to make their content obvious and to warn users under the age of 18 that they are not welcome to view our Web sites, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision of their children's internet use. Nevertheless, we will take any steps possible to discourage those under the age of 18 from visiting our Web sites. 

If you choose to subscribe to one of WASTELAND's websites as a "Member," your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, and IP address are stored by our billing company. This site is an external entity, and once this information is transmitted to them we are under no obligation to police their use of the information, and take no steps to do so. All of the aforementioned information, with the exception of your credit card information, is also stored on our servers.  If you wish to have your information completely removed from our servers, our fraud policies require that we maintain at least your customer name and minimal identifying information. All other information can be deleted.

WASTELAND's Commitment to Data Security

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.  In the event of a breach, you will be notified immediately.

Where to Direct Questions about WASTELAND's Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact our Customer Service Department at support@wasteland.com.
